Hello everyone, this is Haruka Koizumi, aka Oharu.
Today, I'm going to answer the questions I received from Hito-chan.
So, I've been doing a project where 22-year-old Haruka answers 5 questions from all 5 members.
This is the last one, Hito-chan's version.
Hito-chan sent us her question!
Look, there is a tiny Hito-chan here!
I thought it was so tiny, and then I saw it on the screen, and I thought, "It's so tiny!
So I put HITO-chan on the screen.
Thank you very much for your interest in the questions project.
This is the last of the questions.
I'd like to answer your questions now!
Let's go!
Hitoka, I'm going to get angry!
I haven't seen you around much lately.
So, I'd like to answer some of your questions, many of which are filled with Hito-chan's need for approval.
First of all, what do you think is cute about Hitoka?
Well, you're already cute by the time you sent me this question, but I've already asked you what you think is cute about Hito-chan.
What do you think is cute about Hito-chan?
I like your voice.
I like your strong voice when you do "aori" at live performances.
But I also like Hito-chan's voice that's a little more laid-back.
Like Hachitaro's.
Huh? Isn't it similar? You know, you sound like a baby, Hito-chan.
I like that kind of voice.
And your face is cute, too.
The shape of her feet? My best friend says you have the most beautiful feet.
And Hito-chan's legs are also very slender.
I don't know... they're so thin that they look like you don't have to restrict your diet too much.
Hito-chan looks very healthy and thin. You're an amazing HITO-chan.
I think Hito-chan is very attractive because she used to be a model.
Also, the way she makes facial expressions.
There is an accessory brand called "Leo" produced by Hito-chan.
When I saw the visual of the brand, I thought Hito-chan's expression was really wonderful.
I'll go on to Hito-chan's favorite part from the latest Love Iyaki single.
My favorite song in Love Iyaki is "Absolute Dayo"!
Hito-chan's "It's Definitely You" seems to have somehow caught on to me.
The lyrics of "I've been teasing you about your lonely nature, but before I know it, you've caught my reflection, too" and the lyrics of "What do you want as a present?
What do you want for a present? I used to have trouble answering, but now I can clearly say, I want you to give me your love.
I like these two parts.
Maybe I was a bit stubborn at the time...
She was making fun of her lonely nature, but I guess I saw it in her too.
And when he asked me what I wanted as a present, I thought, "I don't know what I want.
But now that he's gone, I want your love.
It makes me want to cry.
The expression on Hito-chan's face when she sings that part is amazing.
It's so sad and fragile, but there's something about the way she's smiling.
Her sad smile is so beautiful.
I also really like the lyrics.
I also like the lyrics of Love Ear Yaki's "Say Yes, I Love You" and the last song "Fluttering Flutter".
And the part where you say "Hirahirahirahira" at the end of "Hirahirahirahira" is really great.
I wish you all the best!
Third, what do you think has changed in the 8 years you've been living next to each other?
I've been standing next to you for 8 years and I think you've changed.
But when I look at Hito-chan's old videos...
I don't know, it's a little awkward.
It's like she's just trying her best, but now...
But now, I wonder if it's more like she's an adult or something.
It's hard to put into words.
But it's like she's very independent, I don't know how to put it.
It's not that I wasn't independent in the past.
I used to feel like I was a little bit overachieving.
But now that we've been active for 8 years, or more than 8 years...
I think that now that we've been active for more than 8 years, we've both become a little more mature.
I used to be quite active in the past, and I'm still active now.
I'm still working hard, but I don't know...
I don't know how to say it.
You know? You know...
I'm Haruka Koizumi, remember?
But now it's Haruka Koizumi.
Understand? I guess I've grown up.
That's what I wanted to say.
Well, fourth...
What ramen do you recommend the most?
What ramen restaurant do you recommend?
Well, Hito-chan often asks me for recommendations for ramen shops.
I have a favorite ramen shop.
This place
Sapporo Miso Ramen Restaurant
This Sapporo Miso Ramen restaurant is called Kitano Daichi.
Their Sapporo Miso Butter Ramen
Miso Butter Corn Ramen was delicious!
And then there's a ramen shop called Hayashida in Shinjuku.
Hayashida ramen shop in Shinjuku is also delicious!
I love that place too!
I've been to a lot of ramen shops!
This is a certain ramen store in Shinbashi.
It's also delicious!
Niboshi Ramen
When I went to eat here, I had ramen.
but there was a guy eating tsukemen next to me
It looked so delicious!
I want to try tsukemen next time I go there!
Here is the last question from Hito-chan.
If you could be Hitokan, what would you do?
If I could be Hitokan
If I could become a Hitokan...
What?
What would you do if you could become a human being?
But maybe I'd like to hear your back once.
Wait, you said that really loud!Wait, that was really loud.
Maybe I'd like to hear her backside once.
I don't know, Haruka Koizumi...
It takes courage.
Yes, but Hitoka Sakai...
I'd like to hear her back.
I'd like to hear her back and eat yakiniku.
That Hitomi... yakiniku.
I've told you 10 million times how much I like you.
As a reward for liking her.
I was taken to yakiniku
by a staff member
You were wearing a backless dress to the barbecue restaurant.
Hito-chan was wearing a backless dress.
I thought it was amazing.
I was genuinely impressed that she would come to a yakiniku barbecue dressed like an adult.
I thought it was amazing, and I'd like to try it.
I thought it was nice.
I'd love to do that.
But when I was making that short video.
I thought, "I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I saw that hoodie, that red hoodie underneath.
I felt sorry for him.
Okay, so...
Hito-chan asked me a question.
Thank you Hito-chan!
Oh, no!
Oh, no.
I'm sorry for falling asleep, Hito-chan.
Okay, thank you very much.
I'd like to do this kind of project again.
I'd like to do another one where we ask for applications from everyone, or we ask the members to appear.
Please look forward to it!
Thank you Hito-chan!
Oh, Hito-chan, you're so cute!
So, I answered your questions today.
Thanks for sending in your questions, Hito-chan!
See you in the next video!
If you liked today's video
If you liked today's video, please click the "Good" button and subscribe to our channel!
See you next time!
Bye bye!
Subscribe to our channel!